Finding Aid for the Anne Waldman Papers, 1945-2012
Anne Waldman Papers
Artists' books.; Audiotapes.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Drafts (documents); Drawings.; Manuscripts for publication.; Manuscripts.; Paintings.; Photographs.; Poems.; Posters.; Slides (photographs).; Student projects.; Videotapes.
Subjects:
Boulder (Colo.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; New York (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; United States.--Intellectual life--20th century.; Abbott, Keith, 1944-; Abrams, Sam; Alcalay, Ammiel; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; Andrews, Bruce, 1948-; Antler, 1946-; Ashbery, John, 1927-; Ball, Gordon; Banks, Russell, 1940-; Baraka, Amina; Baraka, Imamu Amiri, 1934-; Baxter, Glen; Beltrametti, Franco; Berkson, Bill; Bernstein, Charles, 1950-; Berrigan, Ted; Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1947-; Bly, Robert; Bockris, Victor, 1949-; Boudin, Jean; Brainard, Joe, 1942-1994; Brand, Stewart; Brautigan, Richard; Bremser, Bonnie, 1939-; Brook, Donna, 1944-; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000; Brownstein, Michael, 1943-; Bukowski, Charles; Burckhardt, Rudy; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Bye, Ambrose; Bye, Reed; Cage, John; Carroll, Jim; Chr?ibkova´, Marie, 1969-; Clark, Tom, 1941-; Clay, Steven, 1951-; Codrescu, Andrei, 1946-; Cohen, Ira; Collom, Jack, 1931-; Coolidge, Clark, 1939-; Cope, David,, 1948-; Corso, Gregory; Creeley, Robert, 1926-2005; Denby, Edwin, 1903-1983; Di Prima, Diane; Dorn, Edward; Duncan, Robert Edward, 1919-1988; Dunn, Douglas; Dworkin, Andrea; Dylan, Bob, 1941-; Eigner, Larry, 1927-; Elmslie, Kenward; Eshleman, Clayton; Fagin, Larry; Faithfull, Marianne; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Field, Thalia,, 1966-; Ford, Charles Henri; Foss, Phillip; Foye, Raymond, 1957-; Galassi, Jonathan; Gallup, Dick, 1941-; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Giorno, John; Glassgold, Peter, 1939-; Goldberg, Natalie; Greenwald, Ted; Grooms, Red; Guest, Barbara; Gustafson, Jim; Guston, Philip, 1913-1980; Hall, Donald, 1928-; Hawkins, Bobbie Louise, 1930-; Hejinian, Lyn; Heller, Michael, 1937-; Hershon, Robert; Hiler, Jerome.; Hollo, Anselm; Holman, Bob, 1948-; Hornick, Lita R., 1927-; Horowitz, Michael, 1938-; Hoyem, Andrew; Jacquette, Yvonne, 1934-; Johns, Jasper, 1930-; Johnston, Alastair, 1950-; Katz, Alex, 1927-; Kelly, Robert, 1935-; Kerouac, Jan, 1952-; Kesey, Ken; Kinnel, Galway.; Koch, Kenneth, 1925-2002; Kornblum, Allan, 1949-; Kostelanetz, Richard; Kyger, Joanne; Lacy, Steve; LeFevre, Frances; Lenhart, Gary; Lesniak, Rose, 1955-; LeSueur, Joe; Levertov, Denise, 1923-1997; Levine, Les, 1935-; Lifshin, Lyn; Mac Low, Jackson; MacAdams, Lewis, 1944-; Malanga, Gerard; Mapplethorpe, Robert; Mayer, Bernadette; McClure, Michael; McGrath, Thomas, 1916-1990; McNaughton, Duncan; Meltzer, Richard; Merwin, W. S., (William Stanley), 1927-; Mikolowski, Ann; Mikolowski, Ken; Moore, Honor, 1945-; Morice, Dave, 1946-; Myles, Eileen; Nations, Opal L.; Nemerov, Howard; Noel, Susan; North, Charles, 1941-; Notley, Alice, 1945-; Oliver, Akilah; Oliver, Douglas; Oppenheimer, Joel, 1930-1988; Orlovsky, Peter, 1933-2010; Osman, Jena; Padgett, Ron, 1942-; Patchen, Mirian.; Perloff, Marjorie; Rakosi, Carl, 1903-2004; Reed, Ishmael, 1938-; Reed, Lou; Ricard, Rene, 1946-; Richey, Joseph; Rivers, Larry, 1925-2002; Rockwell, Martha.; Rosenquist, James, 1933-; Rosenthal, Bob, 1950-; Rothenberg, Jerome, 1931-; Sakaki, Nanao; Sanders, Ed; Saroyan, Aram; Scalapino, Leslie; Schelling, Andrew; Schiff, Harris; Schjeldahl, Peter; Schneeman, George; Schuyler, James; Shepard, Sam, 1943-; Sike´liano`s, Eleni; Silliman, Ronald, 1946-; Smedman, Lorna; Smith, Pat.; Smith, Patti; Snyder, Gary, 1930-; Swenson, Cole, 1955-; Swenson, May; Talese, Gay; Tanner, Wesley B.; Tarn, Nathaniel; Taylor, Steven.; Thomas, Lorenzo, 1944-2005; Torregian, Sotère; Trungpa, Cho¨gyam, 1939-1987; Tysh, Christine.; Tysh, George, 1942-; Veitch, Tom; Vogelsang, Arthur; Wakoski, Diane; Wang, Ping, 1957-; Warsh, Lewis; Washington, Jerome, 1939-; Whalen, Philip; Wieners, John, 1934-2002; Wilentz, Ted; Wilkie, Britton; Wright, Rebecca, 1942-; Yates, Katie; Zweig, Ellen, 1947-; American poetry -- 20th century.; Artists -- United States.; Authors and publishers.; Beat generation -- United States.; Bohemianism -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Buddhism and education -- United States.; Experimental poetry, American.; Oral interpretation of poetry.; Performance art -- United States.; Poetics.; Poetry -- Study and teaching.; Poetry -- United States.; Poetry.; Poets, American.; Politics and literature.; Social change in literature.; Spiritual life--Buddhism--United States.; Women authors, American.; Women poets, American.; Women publishers--United States.
- Biographical
  The Biographical series is comprised of approximately .5 linear feet of material. The series contains biographical summaries written by Waldman and others, resumes, travel and work itineraries, and publicity material such as press releases, pamphlets, and quotes and "blurbs" for books.
  - Biographical summaries and statements, undated (Box 1)
  - Contemporary Authors autobiographical essay and manuscripts, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Publicity packets, flyers and pamphlets, 1974-2004, undated (Box 1)
  - Press releases and reviews, 1970-2004, undated (Box 1)
  - Quotes and "blurbs," undated (Box 1)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 1)
  - Travel and work itineraries, 2002, 2006 and undated (Box 1)
  - Various poems about Anne Waldman, 1986-1998, undated (Box 1)
  - Tributes (Box 1)
  - Columbia Spectator newspaper with annotations by Jonathan Cott, September-December, 1962 (Box 1)
  - U.S. passport, January 18, 1978 - January 17, 1983 (Box 1)
- Correspondence and Name File
  The Correspondence and Name File series consists of 25 linear feet of material, divided into several subseries. The series provides insight into Waldman's professional activities and relationships, and her personal relationships with an astounding number of poets, writers, and artists.
  - Name File
    - Abbott, Keith, 1990, 2000-2001, undated (Box 2)
    - Abbott, Steve, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Abish, Walter, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Abrams, Michael, 1972-1981, undated (Box 2)
    - Abrams, Sam
      - Correspondence, 1977-1997 (Box 2)
      - Manuscripts, 1989-1994 (Box 2)
    - Acconci, Vito, undated (Box 2)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1973-1977 (Box 2)
    - Adam, Helen, 1976-1986, undated (Box 2)
    - Alcalay, Ammiel (3 folders), 2004-2009 (Box 2)
    - Aletti, Vince, undated (Box 2)
    - Allen, Deborah, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Allen, Donald, 1968-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Allen, Michael, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Allione, Tsultim and Constanzo, 1978-1982, undated (Box 2)
    - Alpert, Barry, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - Amussen, Robert (The Bobbs-Merrill Company), 1968-1980 (Box 2)
    - Anania, Michael, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Anderson, Erik, 1992, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Anderson, Laurie, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Andre, Michael, undated (Box 2)
    - Andrews, Bruce
      - Correspondence, 1971-1989 (Box 2)
      - Manuscripts and printed, 1986, undated (Box 2)
    - Anglesey, Zoe, 1986-1992 (Box 2)
    - Antler, 1975-1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Aponte, Carlos, undated (Box 2)
    - Ardinger, Rick (Limberlost Press), 1992 (Box 2)
    - Aronowitz, Al, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Ashbery, John
      - Correspondence, 1966-1992 (Box 2)
      - Poetry photocopies, undated (Box 2)
      - Flyer and introduction, undated (Box 2)
    - Ashley, Robert, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Atlas, James, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Augustine, Jane, 1986-1996, 2004 (Box 2)
    - Autin, David, 1973, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Ayden, Erje, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Ayers, Ian, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Balash, Muriel (WCBS-TV), 1975 (Box 2)
    - Baldwin, Gordon, 1974-1996, undated (Box 2)
    - Ball, Gordon
      - Correspondence, 1974-1991, 2000, 2007 (Box 2)
      - Portfolio: Selected Photographs of the Beat Generation, photocopy 1994 (Box 2)
    - Ballou, Ronald (The Chapel Press), 1971 (Box 2)
    - Bamber, Linda (Tufts University), 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bamberger, Bill and Janet (2 folders), 1975-1997, 2000, undated (Box 2)
    - Banks, Russell, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
    - Baraka, Amiri and Amina, 1977-2004, undated (Box 2)
    - Barba, Sharon and Joanna Cattonar (University of New Mexico), 1980 (Box 2)
    - Bardwell, Leland, undated (Box 2)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Bartlett, Lee ( American Poetry Review ), 1984-1985, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Bathurst, Bill, 1969-1988, undated (Box 2)
    - Baude, Dawn, 1993-1995 (Box 2)
    - Baxter, Glen, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - Becher, Anne, 1987, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Beck-Rex, Marguerite, 1976 (Box 2)
    - Beltrametti, Franco, 1977-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Benamov, Michel, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Benn, Soyo, 1979, undated (Box 2)
    - Berg, Karen, undated (Box 2)
    - Berge, Carol, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Berke, Roberta, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Berkson, Bill
      - Manuscripts, 1968, undated (Box 2)
      - Printed and miscellaneous, 1973, 1974 and undated (Box 2)
      - Correspondence (6 folders), 1966-2006, undated (Box 3)
    - Berman, Paul, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1979-1992, 2004, undated (Box 3)
    - Berrigan, Anselm, 1994, 2000-2004 (Box 3)
    - Berrigan, David and Kate, 1982-2004, undated (Box 3)
    - Berrigan, Edmund, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Berrigan, Sandy
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1987, 2000, 2004, undated (Box 3)
      - Manuscripts, 1969, undated (Box 3)
    - Berrigan, Ted
      - Correspondence (2 folders) 1966-1983, undated (Box 3)
      - Manuscripts
        - Poetry, undated (Box 3)
        - Prose, 1970, undated (Box 3)
      - Printed material, 1969-1971, undated (Box 3)
      - Lectures and Teaching material, 1976, undated (Box 3)
      - Flyers and artwork, undated (Box 3)
      - Clippings, 1983, undated (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967, undated (Box 3)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei
      - Correspondence, 1982-1998, 2002, undated (Box 3)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 3)
    - Bertholf, Robert (University of Buffalo), 1995-1996 (Box 3)
    - Bey, Hakim, undated (Box 3)
    - Billote, Louise, 1977, undated (Box 3)
    - Blackburn, Paul, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Blake, Bill, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Blaser, Robin, 1992-1993, 2000, undated (Box 3)
    - Bly, Robert, 1974-1977 (Box 3)
    - Bockris, Victor, 1974-1980, undated (Box 3)
    - Bodien, Richard, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Boelitz, Martin, 1962-1964, undated (Box 3)
    - Bonanno, David (American Poetry Review), 1988 (Box 3)
    - Bootman, Tyler, undated (Box 3)
    - Borregard, Angela, undated (Box 3)
    - Borrus, Beth, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Boudin, Jean and Leonard, 1975-1986, undated (Box 3)
    - Bowering, George, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Boyack, Jimmy, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Boyers, Marion, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Bradshaw, David, 1997 (Box 3)
    - Brainard, Joe
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1967-1991, undated (Box 3)
      - Correspondence (5 folders), 1967-1991, undated (Box 4)
      - Manuscripts
        - I Remember (2 folders), undated (Box 4)
        - "Little Known Facts About People," undated (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous manuscripts, 1972, undated (Box 4)
      - Printed material, 1972-1994, undated (Box 4)
      - Interview by Anne Waldman, 1978, undated (Box 4)
      - Obituary and memorial, 1994 (Box 4)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 4)
      - Flyers and ephemera, 1987, undated (Box 4)
      - Finding Aid for Joe Brainard Archive, Mandeville Department of Special Collections, University of California, San Diego, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Braman, Sandra, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Bramness, Hanne, 1982-1993 (Box 4)
    - Brand, Stewart, 1975-1978 (Box 4)
    - Brautigan, Richard, 1970, undated (Box 4)
    - Bremser, Bonnie
      - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 4)
      - Manuscript of memoir, undated (Box 4)
    - Bremser, Ray, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Brenner, Summer, 1979, undated (Box 4)
    - Brody, Jim, 1966-1979, undated (Box 4)
    - Brook, Donna, 1973, undated (Box 4)
    - Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1973, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Brooks, Steve, undated (Box 4)
    - Broughton, James, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Broumas, Olga, 1992-1995, undated (Box 4)
    - Brown, Lee Ann (The Poetry Project), 1989-1990, 2002, undated (Box 4)
    - Brown, Rebecca, 1973-1984, undated (Box 4)
    - Brownstein, Michael
      - Correspondence (6 folders), 1966-2000, undated (Box 4)
      - Manuscripts, 1980, undated (Box 4)
      - Printed material, undated (Box 4)
      - Notes for Anne Waldman, undated (Box 5)
      - Notes, jottings and miscellaneous, undated (Box 5)
    - Bruck, Rolf, 1986-1991 (Box 5)
    - Bruckner, Don, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Buchanan, Ann, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Bukowski, Charles, 1971-1978 (Box 5)
    - Bunge, Nancy, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Bunting, Basil, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Burch, Marcia (Penguin Books), 1973 (Box 5)
    - Burckhardt, Rudy, 1967-1995, undated (Box 5)
    - Burger, Mary, undated (Box 5)
    - Burk, Ronnie, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Burns, Skip, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Burroughs, William
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1976-1996, undated (Box 5)
      - Interview by Anne Waldman, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Post cards, announcements and clippings, undated (Box 5)
      - Funeral and memorial, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Bush, Rebecca, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Butts, Wally, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Bye, Reed
      - Correspondence
        - Anne Waldman (6 folders), 1976-2001, 2006, undated (Box 5)
        - Other correspondents (6 folders), 1971-1987, undated (Box 5)
      - Manuscripts
        - "Border Theme", undated (Box 5)
        - "Poems 1978" (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous poems and notes, 1979, undated (Box 5)
        - Journal entries, 1979-1980, undated (Box 5)
        - Heart's Bestiary cover mock-ups, undated (Box 5)
      - Naropa Course notes, 1981 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979, 2002, undated (Box 5)
    - Caddel, Richard, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Cage, John, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Campbell, Marc (Lodestar Press), undated (Box 5)
    - Cantrill, Arthur and Corrine, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Cardarelli, Joe, 1989-1992 (Box 5)
    - Carella, Simone, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Carey, Steve, 1971, undated (Box 5)
    - Carey, Tom, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Carroll, Jim
      - Correspondence, 1969-1974, undated (Box 5)
      - Manuscripts (2 folders), 1982, undated (Box 5)
    - Carroll, Paul, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
    - Carson, Anne, 2005 (Box 5)
    - Carstairs, Jaime, 1974-1998, undated (Box 5)
    - Cerevalo, Joe, 1986, undated (Box 5)
    - Cheatham, David, 1980, undated (Box 6)
    - Chester, Laura, 1987-1990 (Box 6)
    - Chribkova, Marie (One Woman Press), 2001 (Box 6)
    - Clark, Angelica, 1970-1975, 2000-2006, undated (Box 6)
    - Clark, Tom
      - Correspondence (4 folders), 1965-1995, 2001, undated (Box 6)
      - Manuscripts
        - Poetry, 1971-1986, undated (Box 6)
        - Prose, undated (Box 6)
      - Printed material, 1971, undated (Box 6)
      - Artwork, 1968-1970, undated (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968, undated (Box 6)
    - Clay, Steve (Granary Books), 1996-2001, undated (Box 6)
    - Cleamon, Peter, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Cobb, Noel, 1974-1975, undated (Box 6)
    - Codrescu, Andrei
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1969-1995, undated (Box 6)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 6)
    - Cohen, Ira, 1986-1992, undated (Box 6)
    - Cohen, Jonathan, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Cohn, Jim
      - Correspondence, 1978-2001, undated (Box 6)
      - Manuscripts, 1981, undated (Box 6)
    - Coleman, Victor, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Collom, Jack
      - Correspondence, 1971-1994, 2005-2006 (Box 6)
      - Manuscripts
        - "Answering Something Plato Said," 1988 (Box 6)
        - 'The Blue Heron," undated (Box 6)
        - "The Drift of Things," 1978 (Box 6)
        - "Haiku in Great Literature of the West," undated (Box 6)
        - "Travel South in the Summer," 1978 (Box 6)
        - "Trip to Mexico," 1979 (Box 6)
        - "Winning," undated (Box 6)
        - "8-Ball," 1992 (Box 6)
        - Miscellaneous poems (2 folders), 1978-1987, undated (Box 6)
      - Poster and broadsides, 1988, undated (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6)
    - Colville, Georgiana, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Connor, Julia, 1989-2002 (Box 6)
    - Cook, Albert, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Coolidge, Clark
      - Correspondence, 1971-1994, undated (Box 6)
      - Manuscripts
        - "The Crystal Text," undated (Box 6)
        - Ted Berrigan material, 1983 (Box 6)
        - Miscellaneous manuscripts, 1973-1982, undated (Box 6)
      - Interview questionnaire, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1979-1982, undated (Box 6)
    - Cope, David, 1985-1998, 2001-2002 (Box 6)
    - Corbett, Bill, 1973-1997, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Corman, Cid, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Corso, Gregory, 1971, 1977, undated (Box 6)
    - Cott, Jonathan
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1962-1994, 2002, undated (Box 7)
      - Manuscripts, 1980-1986, undated (Box 7)
    - Coultas, Brenda, 2001, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Cox, Bill, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
    - Crabtree, Lee, 1968-1973, undated (Box 7)
    - Creeley, Robert
      - Correspondence, 1971-1997, undated (Box 7)
      - University of New Mexico M.A. thesis, Selected Poems (1957-1959), 1959 (Box 7)
      - Printed Material, 1973-1984 (Box 7)
    - Creson, Steve, 1987-1993 (Box 7)
    - Curtis, Jackie, undated (Box 7)
    - Crispell, Marilyn 2001-2002 (Box 7)
    - Daley, John, 1977, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Dalrymple-Hollo, Jane, 1984, undated (Box 7)
    - Dardzinski, Dennis, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Darras, Jaques, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Dart, Melinda, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Davidson, Michael, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
    - Davies, Alan, 1975-1995 (Box 7)
    - Davis, Gray Harriman, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Davison, Matthew, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Dawson, Fielding, 1974-1994 (Box 7)
    - DeCoursey, Peggy, 1975, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Degroote, Bernard, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Della Terza, Grazia, 1984-1987, 2002 (Box 7)
    - De Loach, Allen (Empire State College), 1971-1977 (Box 7)
    - DeLynn, Jane, undated (Box 7)
    - Dematrakis, Johanna, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Denby, Edwin
      - Correspondence, 1973-1979, undated (Box 7)
      - Manuscripts, 1981, undated (Box 7)
      - Interview, 1978 (Box 7)
      - Biographical, 1974-1997 (Box 7)
    - Dennis, Donna, 1974-1984, undated (Box 7)
    - Desjardins, Marc, undated (Box 7)
    - Devore, Darrell, undated (Box 7)
    - DeWys, Margaret, 1984 (Box 7)
    - DiPietro, Robert (Lordly & Dame, Inc.), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Dibbell, Charlie, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Di Prima, Diane
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1974-2012, undated (Box 7)
      - Manuscripts, 1975-1988, undated (Box 7)
      - Printed Material, 1976-1984, undated (Box 7)
      - Course and workshop descriptions, 1987, undated (Box 7)
    - di Prima, Jeanne, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Disch, Tom, undated (Box 7)
    - Dmytriw, Linda, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Dominic, Magie, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Donegan, Pat, 1980-1984 (Box 7)
    - D'Or, Vic, (The Eternal Network), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Dorfman, Elisa, 1975, undated (Box 7)
    - Dorje, Shakya, 1977-1980, undated (Box 7)
    - Dorn, Ed
      - Correspondence, 1974-1992 (Box 7)
      - Printed material, 1971-1987 (Box 7)
    - Dorn, Harold, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Dorsky, Nick
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1970-1994, 2009, undated (Box 7)
      - Manuscript, undated (Box 7)
      - Biographical, undated (Box 7)
    - Douthit, Peter (World Poetry Bout Association), 1994 (Box 7)
    - Dragonette, Ree, undated (Box 7)
    - Ducornet, Rikki, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Duncan, Robert
      - Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box 7)
      - Interviews, 1978, undated (Box 7)
    - Dunn, Douglas
      - Correspondence (4 folders), 1975-2001, undated (Box 8)
      - Correspondence (7 folders), 1975-2001, undated (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts, 1997 (Box 8)
      - Postcards, flyers, and announcements, 1987-1988, undated (Box 8)
      - Artwork, undated (Box 8)
    - Dunn, Ethan, 1986, undated (Box 8)
    - Dunn, S.K., 1978, undated (Box 8)
    - Dunning, Steven, 1977, undated (Box 8)
    - Duplessis, Rachel Blau, 1995-1997, 2001, 2004 (Box 8)
    - DuRoi, Denise, 1981-1983, undated (Box 8)
    - Dworkin, Andrea, 1965, undated (Box 8)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1986, undated (Box 8)
    - Einhorn, Nikolaus (S Press Tonbanduerlag), 1979 (Box 8)
    - Eisenberg, Barry, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
    - Ekner, Reidar, 1978-1983 (Box 8)
    - Elisov, Tania
      - Correspondence, 1990-1998, undated (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts, 1993-1998, undated (Box 8)
    - Emigholz, Heinz, 1979 (Box 8)
    - Elliot, Jai, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Ellison, John (Broken Moon Press), 1993 (Box 8)
    - Elmslie, Kenward
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1969-1994, undated (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts
        - "City Junket," undated (Box 8)
        - Poetry, 1969, undated (Box 8)
        - Biographies and writing exercises, 1968, undated (Box 8)
      - Printed Material, 1970-1977 (Box 8)
      - Posters and Flyers, undated (Box 8)
    - Elovich, Richard, 1976-1980 (Box 8)
    - Epstein, Jason (Random House), 1980 (Box 8)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1971-2006, undated (Box 8)
    - Facey, Steve, 1972-1977, undated (Box 8)
    - Fagin, Larry
      - Correspondence, 1969-1994, 2001, undated (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts, 1968-1969, undated (Box 8)
      - Interview(?), undated (Box 8)
      - "Proust Questionnaire" completed by Anne Waldman, 1971 (Box 8)
      - Broadsides, posters, and artwork, 1977, undated (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8)
    - Faithfull, Marianne, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - Farrah, George, 1973 (Box 8)
    - Faulwell, Dean, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Feliu, Denise, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Felver, Chris, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence
      - Correspondence, 1974-1994, 2001-2003, undated (Box 8)
      - Manuscripts and printed material, 1975-1994, undated (Box 8)
    - Ferrari, Mary
      - Correspondence, 1969-1993 (Box 9)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 9)
    - Field, Edward, 1977 (Box 9)
    - Field, Thalia, 1999-2003 (Box 9)
    - Fielding, Kent, undated (Box 9)
    - Fischer, Norman, 1981-1995 (Box 9)
    - Fishbach, Chris (Coffeehouse Press), 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 9)
    - Fisher, Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
    - Fisketjon, Gary (Random House), 1980 (Box 9)
    - Fitzsimmons, Thomas, undated (Box 9)
    - Folkins, Caroline, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1972-1995, undated (Box 9)
    - Foss, Phillip, 1984-1992 (Box 9)
    - Foster, Ed, 1981-1997, undated (Box 9)
    - Fox, Elizabeth, 1978-1985, undated (Box 9)
    - Fox, Siv Cedering, undated (Box 9)
    - Foye, Raymond, 1986-1993 (Box 9)
    - Frankel, Adrienne, 1979, undated (Box 9)
    - Franks, David, 1970-1993, undated (Box 9)
    - Fraser, Kathleen, 1986-2001 (Box 9)
    - Fredricks, Claude, 1966-1977, undated (Box 9)
    - Freilicher, Jane, 1981, undated (Box 9)
    - Friedman, Ed
      - Correspondence, 1986-1993, undated (Box 9)
      - "Desert Industry," manuscript, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Friedman, Jon, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Friedman, Richard, 1972-1974 (Box 9)
    - Friend, Ethelyn (Stearns), 1983-1995 (Box 9)
    - Funkhouser, Christopher, 1997, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Galassi, Jonathan, 1976-1984 (Box 9)
    - Gallup, Dick
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
      - Manuscripts, 1978, undated (Box 9)
    - Galuis, Kristen, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Gardner, Geoffery, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - Garland, Peter
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
      - "The Bone Show," manuscript and score, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Gay, Pamela, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Gere, Richard, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Germaine, Edward, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Gierach, John, undated (Box 9)
    - Gilbert, Alan (2 folders), 2001-2009 (Box 9)
    - Gill, Charles (Archer Press), 1977-1978 (Box 9)
    - Gill, Neil, undated (Box 9)
    - Gillfillan, Merrill, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Gilliat, Sarah, undated (Box 9)
    - Ginsberg, Allen
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1970-1995, undated (Box 9)
      - Manuscripts
        - Howl (labeled "second working copy") (5 folders), 1986 (Box 9)
        - Introduction for William Burroughs' Letters to Allen Ginsberg, 1953-1957, edited by Ron Padgett 1981 (Box 9)